

# Alexey Ryzhov

Front-end Developer

(React/Redux/ TypeScript)

# CONTACT ME AT



Tambov, Russia



fristail27@gmail.com



<u>AlexeyRyzhov</u>



<u> AlexeyRyzhov</u>



<u> AlexeyRyzhov</u>



+7-(980)-671-33-62



My portfolio



**Codewars** 

# LANGUAGES



Pre-intermediate (in progress)

### **PROFILE**

Front-end developer with experience creating SPA using technologies such as: React, TS/JS, Redux, HTML, CSS.My free time is dedicated to Codewars and becoming familiar with NodeJS and Express.js. In the future I see myself as a Full Stack Developer. Ready to consider project work and full-time employment.

# **SKILLS**

React
Redux
TypeScript
JavaScript
REST API
HTML
CSS
StoryBook
Git & GitHub

Material UI, Ant Design, Axios, Unit tests, Jest, TDD, Flux, SASS, BEM, YARN, NPM, ES6, Redux-form, Redux-thunk, Linux, Hooks, HOC

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Freelance Oct 2020 - Present

React development using redux, React-redux, react-router-dom, redux-thunk, redux-toolkit, Axios, Formik, Ant-design libraries.

Work with Hooks, TypeScript.

Refactoring, bug fixing, migrating to TypeScript, registration and login form creation

Reusable components development, jest testing.

#### STRUCTURAL ENGINEER

2012 -2013

Calculation of building structures, creating drawings in AutoCAD, registration of construction documentation

# **EDUCATION**

# TAMBOV STATE TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY 2010 - 2015

Industrial and civil engineering

# **COURSES**

# IT-INCUBATOR

React, Redux, TypeScript, Redux-thunk, Rest API for development of SPA-application.

## **UDEMY 2019 - 2020**

ES6+, Vue.js, OOP, AJAX, Webpack, Jest

NodeJS, MongoDB, GraphQL, MySQL, Express